Director.
Why do you look so unhappy?
I thought I made it clear
to you last night.
Right.
You said so much to me.
I thought you didn't want to cast me,
and were just too embarrassed to say it.
Wasn't that the case?
So,
do you know,
when I received Sister Hu's call last night,
and she said
you decided to cast me as the male lead,
how surprised I was?
Then I figured it out.
You told me
that if I was just trying out the musical
for fun,
I should give up.
But,
am I here just for fun?
No.
I really want to participate in this.
So, Director, you were motivating me
to perform with 100% passion.
Director.
I get it, Director.
You don't understand sh...
Don't worry, Director.
For the role of Ning Caichen,
I've done a lot of research.
It seems
this is not over yet.
OK, Director.
Wu Qiming.
Let me tell you, I'm the boss.
I signed the contract,
so I have the final say.
What are you doing?
Give me the contract.
I won't. Give it to me!
Give it to me!
I won't!
Fine.
If Jin Xi plays Ning Caichen,
then find someone else to direct.
Ning Jin, let me tell you. Don't go.
I have your contract too.
You must follow my arrangements.
If I tell you to direct, you must direct.
I don't care.
You'll tear it!
What are you doing?
I won't give it.
Tear it!
I won't.
I won't! I won't!
Don't move.
Ouch.
Stop faking it.
Give me the contract.
I'm not faking it. I'm not. I'm not.
I strained my back.
Really?
I was clubbing with Boss Shen all night yesterday.
Help... help me up.
Ning Jin.
There is something I need to tell you.
For the play Jianjia,
actually,
we're losing money.
Isn't every show a full house?
To warm up the crowd,
I gave out complimentary tickets.
Over the years, our musicals
have had the highest industry standards
in costumes and art design.
Even your music
is recorded with real instruments,
not synthesized.
Let's be honest,
have I ever said no to any of your requests
all these years?
I have great respect for creators like you.
But me,
I'm not young anymore.
In a few years,
I won't be able to drink
or party anymore.
Investors like Mr. Shen
will also abandon me.
This time, Mr. Shen
didn't plan to invest
in A Chinese Ghost Story at all.
Thanks to Jin Xi joining,
Mr. Shen knows
Jin Xi's traffic and popularity,
so he gave us one last chance.
If A Chinese Ghost Story
doesn't make money,
our troupe
will eventually shut down.
How about
we look for new investors?
Careful.
No need.
I am now
old and fading.
It's hard for me to mingle
in the rich ladies' circle.
I'm not
who I used to be.
The old me,
look at my photos on the wall.
Ning Jin,
just give me a chance,
okay?
I'm telling you,
Jin Xi won't last in this troupe
for even a week.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to our troupe.
I'm really so happy.
I look forward to working with you.
Welcome to the team.
Nice to meet you.
This is my boyfriend.
This is Mr. Du Heying.
His professional skills are
highly reliable.
Jinzi.
The director is coming soon.
Everyone, get ready.
You are bad.
Okay, okay, I'm bad.
I'm bad.
Are you two still being all lovey-dovey?
Jin Xi is coming soon.
Hurry up and tidy up.
So what if he comes? What does it have to do with us?
Exactly.
This is a huge opportunity.
With him joining,
our play is definitely
going to be a hit.
Do you know
why he is performing in a musical?
He's ruined TV dramas,
so now he's coming to ruin musicals.
How can he compare with Mr. Heying?
Don't say that.
Jin Xi's popularity
is something I can't compare to.
Any publicity is good publicity.
I watched two episodes of 'The Legend of Huayue'.
His comfort zone
is my discomfort zone.
I have so many memes of him.
Do you guys want to see?
I'll send them to the group chat.
What is this?
Why do you have memes of other men?
The little guy loves getting angry so much.
Who is the little guy?
Delete it quickly.
Delete this.
What is so interesting?
Morning, director.
Hello, director.
Come on, line up.
Before we rehearse, let me say a few words to everyone.
Originally, I chose Heying
to play the male lead, Ning Caichen,
for this role.
But now,
due to Boss Wu's sudden arrangement,
we have to reassign
everyone's roles.
No problem.
There are no small roles, only small actors.
I'll follow the director's arrangement.
So Heying,
your current role
is the second male lead, Yan Chixia.
At the same time,
I have to ask you to be
the B-cast understudy for Ning Caichen.
No problem.
Master Jiao,
you're reassigned to the role of Ning Caichen's pageboy.
Also, with Mr. Qingsong
You will share the A and B roles of the Black Mountain Demon.
Got it.
The other roles remain unchanged.
Jinxi is here.
Director.
Sorry.
Hello.
I'm a bit late.
I bought coffee for everyone.
Here.
Hand them out.
No need.
Jinxi.
I hope you can be more punctual.
I'm sorry.
Don't let it happen again.
Go stand with everyone else.
Jinxi.
Director,
which scene are we rehearsing today?
No rehearsal today.
Same as usual.
Let's start with the seed exercise.
Qingsong.
Come.
Everyone, take a seat.
Thank you.
Curl up our bodies.
Imagine we are
a seed.
We are
I'm Eason.
buried in the soil.
Xiao Qi.
After four seasons,
What do you do?
we
Stage manager.
are slowly waking up.
Then our jobs are quite similar.
Slowly
How so?
Doing chores and running errands.
waking up.
We feel the environment around us,
the soil,
and the moisture.
We start to slowly
grow.
Yearning for life.
Jinxi,
let's move.
Look at the classmates around you.
Slowly, we are growing.
To the left, to the right.
At this moment, we break through the soil.
We feel the sunlight.
The light shines on our leaves.
We continue to grow.
Suddenly, a fierce wind blows.
We sway in the wind.
At this moment,
lightning flashed, thunder rolled, and heavy rain poured down.
We were slammed to the ground.
We soared into the sky
and turned into birds.
We grew wings.
We started to fly,
to fly.
Higher and higher.
Birds,
fly.
Gradually, we saw the ocean.
We start diving.
We dive into the water.
Into the water,
we become fish.
We start swimming.
Start swimming.
We swim and swim.
Swim and swim.
We jump out of the water
and turn into leopards.
We start running and jumping.
Our lives wither away.
We turn back into that seed.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
Everyone, sit down.
Let's move on
to our next exercise.
The one-sentence exercise.
Big Cousin.
Qingsong.
You two
are playing
an undercover narcotics cop and his informant.
The first sentence is,
"They will never know."
You say the first sentence.
What does 'one sentence' mean?
It means,
given a scenario and two character settings,
two people,
without any prior discussion,
must complete an improv performance.
Is it that impressive?
By the way,
what's your name?
Bai Feixin.
You're the female lead in 'Jianjia'.
I've seen your show.
You're playing the female lead, Nie Xiaoqian, in this play too.
You guessed right, Caichen.
I look forward to working with you.
Three, two, one.
Zhang Wanru.
We all call her Big Cousin.
That's Mr. Qingsong.
He's our dance choreographer.
They will never know.
Were all these lines written beforehand?
Improvisation.
Is it that amazing?
Everyone is a screenwriter.
Improvisation
is a stage actor's
essential skill.
Wanru.
We stand between the masses
and the evil forces,
as the last line of defense.
This is the mission we must complete.
Cut.
Great acting.
Good performance.
Go back to your seats.
Good work.
Next group.
Feixin, Heying.
Yes, director.
You are playing
lovers reuniting after a long time.
The first line is,
"I really didn't expect..."
Thank you.
Okay?
Sure.
Three.
I really didn't expect
you to be doing this kind of work.
So what do you want to say now?
Do you look down on me?
Do you want to scold me,
insult me,
or do you have something else to say?
Feixin.
I love you.
What's the use of saying this now?
Is it too late?
Feixin. Listen to me, Feixin.
Don't touch me.
Feixin, listen to me.
Feixin.
Don't touch me.
I love you.
Feixin, listen to me.
Don't touch me.
I love you.
What's the use
of saying this now?
I love you.
You don't understand me at all.
Stop.
Well done, Feixin.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Heying.
Not bad.
Go back to your seat.
Next group.
Jinxi.
Jiaoye EWE.
Okay.
Good luck, baby.
Come on, bro.
In 3978 AD,
on a planet,
apes became the most intelligent species
on it.
Suddenly one day,
humans arrived on this planet.
The first thing the apes said
after seeing humans was,
Ooh-eeh-ah.
Please begin.
Wu yi ei.
Wu.
Bro.
Cheng Yaojin.
Director,
have a drink.
I don't drink sodas.
Thanks.
Director, you direct musicals so well.
Have you ever considered
switching to being a film director?
Actually,
if you and Jinxi
work well together this time,
please take good care of him.
I have resources for everyone
to get a movie project off the ground.
If you transition to a film director,
not to mention the income,
the influence
is beyond what musicals can compare with.
Sorry.
I just ate,
so I won't have your pie-in-the-sky.
And you just saw,
Jinxi is the one with
the worst conditions among all the actors.
So it's even more impossible for me
to treat him differently from the others
and be lenient with him.
I'm leaving.
Hello?
Looking for Sister Hu? She's not here.
Hello,
Mr. Lai.
That was my assistant just now.
I'm sorry.
Feeling better, bro?
Gentle.
Sister Hu asked me to tell you
that it's still the adaptation stage.
It's normal to be a bit sore and tired.
It won't always be this intense.
Don't worry.
I'm not worried.
This musical is so interesting.
Rehearsing is so fun.
I'll give you a good massage when we get back.
I'm not going back.
I'm going to the zoo to observe chimpanzees.
I am very dissatisfied
with my performance today.
Bro, you're awesome.
I want to be like you.
Ooh ee eh.
Wanwan.
Don't call me Wanwan.
Are you crazy? Don't call me Wanwan.
Don't come over. Don't come over.
Jin Xi.
What are you doing?
Playing a gorilla.
Your gorilla head is quite gorilla-like.
It's just a bit...
Good morning, Big Wanwan.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
Meng Tejiao, who are you hugging?
Morning.
Morning, Director.
What are you doing?
I'm playing an ape.
I can play chimpanzees, bonobos,
orangutans,
gibbons,
and gorillas.
You are not playing an ape today.
Not playing an ape?
What we're doing today is
practicing transitioning from a real-life story to a song.
What is a real-life story?
It's simple.
It's just telling a story about
something in your life
that left a deep impression on you.
Then, based on this story,
what song does it make you think of?
Then sing this song to everyone.
Singing is your comfort zone.
I believe it won't be a problem for you.
Let's begin.
Tell a story?
Yes.
This is the most basic exercise
for musical actors
to transition from dialogue to singing.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Then let's begin.
Tell a story...
Oh, right.
One time, Eason
went to a concert with me.
And he was terrified
by my crazy fan...
Talk about your own experiences.
My own?
My own...
Yes.
One time, Eason and I
went to have hot pot.
Eason, do you remember,
that last time you ordered
a tomato broth,
and they served you a spicy one?
You can't eat spicy food.
And then?
Then that's it.
So, this event,
what song does it remind you of?
It reminds me of
"Spicy Girls".
I'll sing "Spicy Girls".
No need to sing.
Remember what I said just now?
It has to be something that made a deep impression on you,
or
something that influenced your life.
Is it too trivial?
Sister Hu.
Can I talk about
my previous contract termination?
No, you signed an NDA for that.
What about
my crazy fan from before?
Him...
No, you signed one for that too.
If you don't let him say anything,
how can he do this exercise?
Director.
I don't think this is our problem.
It's Jinxi's first time doing this.
Shouldn't someone
demonstrate for him?
Since you love hearing about others' privacy,
why don't you share yours?
I'll do it.
I have a lot of secrets to share.
I remember
one winter...
I...
That won't be necessary.
Feixin, sit down.
I'll share mine then.
Jinxi, sit back down.
Then let me tell you guys
about my life's
terrible relationship history.
In my entire life,
I've had three relationships.
Each one ended
worse than the last.
Xiaoqi.
My first relationship
was with a senior from the college music department.
We admired each other
and got along perfectly.
Although we were both poor at the time,
we were very happy.
We would squeeze into
our shared apartment to watch "Moulin Rouge!".
We agreed to start a business together.
But after graduation,
he signed a contract
with a female agent.
The agent promised to make him famous.
But instead of getting famous,
he ended up with
a bright red lipstick mark on his collar.
So,
I made his favorite game console...
That was just an accident.
fly out the window.
My second relationship
was with the leading actor
I worked with in a musical.
He loved to smile
and always wore white.
Although I'm not short,
he was
1.9 meters tall.
So in his arms,
I looked petite.
I hoped all winter
I could be wrapped up
in his warm coat.
We watched shows
and fireworks together.
I thought I would be happy forever.
Until one day when I was shopping,
I ran into
his other girlfriend.
At that time, we asked him together,
"Who exactly is your girlfriend?"
And his genius response was,
"What do you think?"
Then
he swaggered off.
My third relationship
was with a blind date.
Because my mom wanted me
to settle down.
To settle down.
He was mature and steady,
and successful in his career.
Except for
not telling me
he wasn't divorced yet,
everything was so perfect.
That was really just an accident.
If that's what you think, there's nothing I can do.
I'll get divorced sooner or later.
That was really just an accident.
Get lost!
How is it?
Are you satisfied?